So here's the code that we need to finish.
这是我们要完成的代码
We need a test condition for the while, and in this case
我们需要一个 while 的测试条件
we really want to keep on going forever until we're done.
我们希望在结束前程序能不断运行
So, we're going to use while True and then use break to stop the loop.
所以我们将用 while True  然后用 break 来中断循环
The test condition is true, and the way we know when we're done is when
测试条件为真
the value returned as the URL was none.
当返回的 URL 值为 none 时 程序就结束了
That means we got to the else, so to finish,
这意味着 我们要进行到 else 才能结束
we need to finish the else block by using break.
我们要用 break 来结束 else 程序块
Now let's test our code.
现在让我们来测试一下这些代码
We'll call print_all_links with our test string
我们将调用 print_all_links (打印所有链接)
that has test 1, test 2,
测试字符串里有 test 1,test 2
and test 3 as the 3 links.
和 test 3这3个链接
And when we run this, what we see is it prints out the 3 links,
运行这些代码 我们就会看到这3个链接被打印出来
test 1, test 2, and test 3.
test 1, test 2和test 3
We'll try a more interesting test.
下面我们做一个更有趣的测试
For a more interesting example, let's go back to the web page
我们回到这个网页
we looked at earlier.
我们之前看过的
This was the page with the flying Python comic.
页面上有 python 漫画
And it has many links in it,
还有很多链接
and we saw when we did view source we can see
当我们查看源代码
what those links look like,
我们就能看到这些链接到底是什么样
so the first link that we see on the page.
这就是我们在页面上看到的第一个链接
So if we use Command-F [or Ctrl-F], we can search for the first link on the page.
如果我们使用 F 命令 我们就能搜索页面上的第一个链接
We see that we have these links.
我们看到这些链接
The first one is the link to Archive,
第一个是 Archive (档案馆) 的链接
and that corresponds to what we see here at the top of the page.
这和我们在页面顶部看到的是对应的
Here's the link to Archive, the link to Blag,
这是 Archive 的链接 Blag 的链接
the link to the Store and About and Forums.
Store (商店) About (关于) 和 Forums (论坛) 的链接
And so there's a lot of links on this page.
这个页面上有很多链接
If we go back to our print_all_links code, we can try to print them all.
回到 print_all_links 代码 我们可以尝试把它们都打印出来
First, let's look at what we actually see when we do get_page
首先 我们来看看 用 get_page (获取页面) 会有什么结果
passing in the URL of xkcd.com/353,
传入 xkcd.com/353 这一 URL
which is the page we were looking at.
也就是我们之前在看的页面
And when we run this, we see a lot of text printed out,
运行这一代码 我们看到很多文本被打印出来
and that's exactly what we saw from view source,
和我们查看源代码时所看到的完全一样
but now that's what we're getting as the result from get_page.
但是这是我们从 get_page 得到的结果
That's the text of the web page.
也就是网页的文本
Not very easy to look at.
看起来不太容易
Instead of using get_page, we'll print all the links on the page
现在我们将打印页面上的所有链接
instead of just printing the whole page out.
而不是打印整个页面
Now we're using our print_all_links procedure
我们要使用 print_all_links 这一过程
to print all the links in the xkcd page.
来打印 xkcd 这一页面上的所有链接
And when we run this, we indeed see all the links on the page.
运行这一代码时 我们确实看到了页面上的所有链接
At least we see most of them.
至少是大部分链接
There are a few that we missed, and we'll talk about that in a later unit,
有一些没有打印出来 我们会在之后的单元里来讲这个问题
but we're seeing many of the links on the page, including the first ones that we saw
但是我们看到了页面上的很多链接 包括我们最先看到的几个
with the Archive and the Blag and the Store link,
Archive Blag 以及 Store 的链接
and we're seeing lots of other links.
我们还看到了很多别的链接
And you can see that we go all the way to the
你们可以看到 我们一直打印到了
Buttercup Festival link and the license link.
Buttercup Festival (金凤花节) 和 license (许可证) 链接
Those are the 2 at the bottom of the page.
这是页面底部的两个链接
This is the link to license,
这是 license 的链接
which was the last one that we printed out.
也是我们打印出来的最后一个链接
So, congratulations are in order.
所以 祝贺大家
You've made it to the end of Unit 2, and I hope
你们已经学完了第二单元
you understand the main concepts that we've seen so far.
我希望你们掌握了我们所学的主要概念
In Unit 1 we saw variables.
在第一单元中 我们学习了变量
We learned about programs.
学习了有关程序的内容
We saw how to do arithmetic.
学习了如何做计算
In Unit 2 we learned about making procedures,
在第二单元中 我们学习了如何写程序
and we learned how to use if to make decisions,
如何利用 if 来做决定
and we saw that those by themselves were enough to do
这些知识就足够写出任何电脑程序了
every possible computer program as Alan Turing showed in the 1930s.
阿兰·图灵在20世纪30年代就证明了这一点
We also learned about while loops,
我们还学习了 while 循环
a way to make it more convenient to do things over again.
从而能更方便地重复做同样的事情
And now we've actually got a really good start on our search engine.
要建立一个搜索引擎  我们现在已经有了一个很好的起点
We can print all the links on the page.
我们可以打印页面上的所有链接
We still don't have our web crawler.
我们还没有网络爬虫
We need to actually collect those links and do something with them.
我们需要收集这些链接并对其进行一些操作
That's what we're going to do in Unit 3, and then in Unit 4, 5, and 6,
这就是我们在之后4个单元里要学习的内容
we'll see how to use the corpus that we've built
我们将学习如何利用我们所建立的语料库
to do useful web searches, but we've come a long way,
来进行有效的网络搜索 但我们已经学了很多了
and I hope we'll see you back soon for Unit 3.
我希望你们会回来继续学习第三单元